Why we record
every client call
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
we record all of
our client
communication we
don't do it to
be creepy we do
it because my
brain cannot
remember over 600
questions a month
it's impossible
and so really to
give our clients
the very best
service possible
we have our email
our text phone
calls and Zoom
meetings are all
recorded with
some sort of AI
and then it's
filed into our
client's Google
Drive folder no
one gets access
to that my
husband Josh
Christian makes
sure that
everything is
super super
secure that's
like his
specialty so no
worries there but
what's great is
that that's our
source of truth